A little shaky.
مهتز قليلاً.
That's better.
هذا أفضل.
Finally get a proper meal.
أخيرًا حصلت على وجبة مناسبة.
You are eating like there's no tomorrow.
أنت تأكل وكأن لا غد لك.
Eating way too much.
تناول الطعام بكميات كبيرة جداً.
My arm's sore from holding it.
ذراعي تؤلمني من حملها.
I didn't ask you to.
لم أطلب منك ذلك.
If I starve myself,
إذا جوعت نفسي،
it's so I'll look perfect at the wedding.
هذا حتى أبدو في أبهى حلة في حفل الزفاف.
You really do look beautiful.
تبدين جميلة حقاً.
And you look strikingly handsome.
وتبدو وسيماً بشكل لافت للنظر.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
the wedding's in three days.
الزفاف بعد ثلاثة أيام.
We need to lock in the guest list.
نحتاج إلى تثبيت قائمة المدعوين.
Any friends or family you want invited,
أي أصدقاء أو أفراد عائلة ترغب بدعوتهم،
I'll add them.
سأضيفهم.
Let me think about it.
دعني أفكر في الأمر.
Anyone I forgot to kill?
هل هناك أي شخص نسيت قتله؟
I know you haven't actually hurt your family.
أعلم أنك لم تؤذي عائلتك بالفعل.
For the time being,
في الوقت الحاضر،
I'll just say
سأقول فقط
you're "mentally unstable".
أنت "غير مستقر عقلياً".
But if one day I can't control
لكن إذا لم أستطع السيطرة على نفسي يوماً ما
those filthy thoughts in my head,
تلك الأفكار القذرة التي تدور في رأسي،
what then?
ماذا بعد ذلك؟
So,
لذا،
I suggest you prepare ahead of time.
أنصحك بالاستعداد مسبقاً.
For example,
على سبيل المثال،
this.
هذا.
How cute.
يا له من شيء لطيف.
It's coated with a high dose of anesthetic.
إنه مغطى بجرعة عالية من المخدر.
Using it is simple.
استخدامه بسيط.
Like this.
مثله.
You're worried I might break the pact anytime, right?
أنت قلق من أنني قد أخلف الاتفاق في أي وقت، أليس كذلك؟
This
هذا
is how you deal with me.
هكذا تتعامل معي.
You're really putting a lot of pressure on me.
أنت تضع عليّ ضغطاً كبيراً حقاً.
You'd better like your wedding gift.
من الأفضل أن تعجبك هدية زفافك.
My wife.
زوجتي.
[Wedding Day]
[يوم الزفاف]
I didn't sleep all night,
لم أنم طوال الليل،
and rushed back just for this.
وعاد مسرعاً من أجل هذا فقط.
Pull the camera back a little.
اسحب الكاميرا للخلف قليلاً.
Let me see how your wedding dress looks.
دعيني أرى كيف يبدو فستان زفافك.
Look at those dark circles.
انظر إلى تلك الهالات السوداء.
Get some rest.
خذ قسطاً من الراحة.
Everything's going smoothly here.
كل شيء يسير على ما يرام هنا.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll be there soon.
سأكون هناك قريباً.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
This lemonade is pretty refreshing.
هذا العصير الليموني منعش للغاية.
As long as you like the taste of this oral anesthetic.
طالما أنك تحب طعم هذا المخدر الفموي.
Go to sleep.
اذهب إلى النوم.
Most people can't last more than ten seconds.
معظم الناس لا يستطيعون الصمود لأكثر من عشر ثوانٍ.
Come in.
ادخل.
This Yin is yours now.
هذا الين ملكك الآن.
Make it quick.
أسرع في ذلك.
Contact me once it's done.
اتصل بي بمجرد الانتهاء.
Yes.
نعم.
Miss Wu?
آنسة وو؟
This is the champagne prepared for the wedding.
هذا هو الشمبانيا المُعدّ لحفل الزفاف.
Who should it be served to?
لمن ينبغي تقديمه؟
Just give it to me. You can go.
أعطني إياه فقط. يمكنك الذهاب.
As long as I can get through this,
طالما أنني أستطيع تجاوز هذا،
and have Mr. Gu drink this at the wedding,
واجعل السيد غو يشرب هذا في حفل الزفاف،
I'll be able to form a pact with him smoothly.
سأتمكن من إبرام اتفاق معه بسلاسة.
You audacious pervert!
يا لك من منحرف جريء!
Black nail polish.
طلاء أظافر أسود.
Xia Yuyan.
شيا يويان.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Looks like it's been tampered with.
يبدو أنه قد تم التلاعب به.
Let's play along with her.
فلنلعب معها.
[Catching the Thief] You audacious pervert!
[الإمساك باللص] أيها المنحرف الجريء!
I've been delayed for so long.
لقد تأخرت لفترة طويلة.
I wonder if my brother has already arrived.
أتساءل إن كان أخي قد وصل بالفعل.
If he finds out the groom isn't Lin Juan, that'll be trouble.
إذا اكتشف أن العريس ليس لين جوان، فسيكون ذلك مشكلة.
Mr. Wu.
السيد وو.
The meeting on approving staff reductions at the border is scheduled
من المقرر عقد اجتماع بشأن الموافقة على تخفيضات الموظفين على الحدود
- at this afternoon. - Mine takes priority.
- بعد ظهر اليوم. - أمري له الأولوية.
There's a batch of equipment at the Bureau that needs replacing.
هناك مجموعة من المعدات في المكتب تحتاج إلى استبدال.
We need you to inspect it on site.
نحتاج منك أن تقوم بفحصه في الموقع.
Everything can wait until my sister's wedding is over.
كل شيء يمكن أن ينتظر حتى ينتهي حفل زفاف أختي.
You'll wait here for me.
ستنتظرني هنا.
You really have a talent for ruining my plans.
لديك موهبة حقيقية في إفساد خططي.
You're the one ruining my wedding.
أنت من أفسد حفل زفافي.
Then let's see who's more capable today.
فلنرى من هو الأكثر كفاءة اليوم.
Luckily, she only passed out.
لحسن الحظ، لم تفقد وعيها إلا قليلاً.
Sleep here until the wedding is over.
نم هنا حتى ينتهي حفل الزفاف.
Please welcome
أهلاً وسهلاً بكم
the bride.
العروس.
What's going on? Why so late?
ما الذي يحدث؟ لماذا كل هذا التأخير؟
Where's the witness? They're not here either.
أين الشاهد؟ إنه ليس هنا أيضاً.
Do I look like a madman right now?
هل أبدو كالمجنون الآن؟
You have no idea how many problems I solved in the last half hour.
ليس لديك أدنى فكرة عن عدد المشاكل التي حللتها في النصف ساعة الماضية.
Anyone else might not even be standing here.
ربما لم يكن أي شخص آخر ليقف هنا أصلاً.
How are you so smart?
كيف أصبحتَ بهذه الذكاء؟
Let's adjust the order of the ceremony.
لنقم بتعديل ترتيب الحفل.
First.
أولاً.
Registration and sealing.
التسجيل والختم.
We'll do what my wife says.
سنفعل ما تقوله زوجتي.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Please proceed with the marriage registration and vows.
يرجى المضي قدماً في إجراءات تسجيل الزواج وتبادل العهود.
Please.
لو سمحت.
[Xie Xinxu]
[شيه شينكسو]
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I'll just clean up.
سأقوم بالتنظيف.
Go on with the ceremony.
أكملوا المراسم.
I'll take Mr. Wu to deal with it.
سأستعين بالسيد وو ليتولى الأمر.
(Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Earlier,
سابقًا،
I missed walking you down the aisle.
لقد افتقدت مرافقتك إلى المذبح.
I can't say I wasn't upset.
لا أستطيع أن أنكر أنني كنت منزعجاً.
I won't feel at ease unless I hand you (Watch on www.kisskh,la or www.kisskh,id) to Support Admin
لن أشعر بالراحة إلا إذا سلمتك (شاهد على www.kisskh.la أو www.kisskh.id) إلى إدارة الدعم
to him myself.
سأوجه كلامي إليه بنفسي.
Here.
هنا.
Turn around.
التف حوله.
Okay.
تمام.
Next, please read your vows.
بعد ذلك، يرجى قراءة عهود الزواج.
From this moment on,
من هذه اللحظة فصاعدًا،
our lives
حياتنا
are bound together forever,
مرتبطين معًا إلى الأبد،
in life and in death.
في الحياة وفي الموت.
Within a finite lifetime,
خلال فترة عمر محدودة،
my love
حبيبي
will know no end.
لن يعرف نهاية.
[Signatures. Xie Xinxu. Wu Nongyu]
[التوقيعات: شيه شين شو، وو نونجيو]
♪A ray of morning sun shines through the cafe curtains♪
♪تتسلل أشعة شمس الصباح عبر ستائر المقهى♪
Let us wish them a lifetime as husband and wife.
فلنتمنى لهما حياة زوجية سعيدة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Congratulations.
تهانينا.
- Congratulations. - Happy wedding.
- ألف مبروك. - زفاف سعيد.
♪Hey, don't plan too far ahead♪
♪مهلاً، لا تخطط للمستقبل البعيد♪
♪The next second might change everything♪
♪ قد تُغير الثانية التالية كل شيء ♪
♪Come on, sway along with the music♪
هيا بنا، تمايلوا مع الموسيقى!
♪Off key becomes a romantic beat♪
♪يتحول اللحن النشاز إلى إيقاع رومانسي♪
♪It's showtime♪
حان وقت العرض!
♪Falling into the unknown♪
♪السقوط في المجهول♪
♪Tonight♪
♪الليلة♪
♪I put on a masquerade mask♪
♪ارتديت قناعًا تنكريًا♪
♪Looking at you♪
♪ أنظر إليك ♪
♪You remind me of a romance film♪
♪أنتِ تُذكرينني بفيلم رومانسي♪
♪All the night♪
♪طوال الليل♪
♪Swimming from sea to shore♪
♪السباحة من البحر إلى الشاطئ♪
♪A fate bound to fall♪
♪مصير محتوم♪
♪Into the light♪
♪إلى النور♪
♪Lost in a captivating opera♪
♪ضائع في أوبرا آسرة♪
♪Frozen within♪
♪متجمد من الداخل♪
♪A melody left by the universe♪
لحنٌ تركه الكون
♪In every time and space♪
♪في كل زمان ومكان♪
♪I will meet you again♪
♪سأراك مجدداً♪
- Good. - Good.
- جيد. - جيد.
Are you alright?
هل أنت بخير؟
Kiss her!
قبّلها!
It's this cold. Why is the air on?
الجو باردٌ جداً. لماذا يعمل المكيف؟
You…
أنت…
You're not feeling well?
ألا تشعر بأنك على ما يرام؟
There was something in the champagne at the wedding.
كان هناك شيء ما في الشمبانيا في حفل الزفاف.
It had to be Xia Yuyan.
لا بد أنها شيا يويان.
It had to be her...
كان لا بد أن تكون هي...
Wait.
انتظر.
She didn't use that kind of drug, did she?
لم تكن تتعاطى هذا النوع من المخدرات، أليس كذلك؟
Drink more water. Try to dilute it.
اشرب المزيد من الماء. حاول تخفيفه.
Looks like it's not enough.
يبدو أن هذا غير كافٍ.
I'll get you a few more bottles.
سأحضر لك بضع زجاجات أخرى.
It won't work.
لن ينجح الأمر.
Then…
ثم…
Then I'll find a doctor to check on you.
سأبحث حينها عن طبيب ليفحصك.
Help me.
ساعدني.
I can't. I…
لا أستطيع. أنا…
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Your scent makes me feel a lot better.
رائحتك تجعلني أشعر بتحسن كبير.
The pendant I gave you,
القلادة التي أهديتك إياها،
are you still wearing it?
هل ما زلت ترتديه؟
[Siyuan]
[سييوان]
Hey.
يا.
Why are you still sleeping at this hour?
لماذا ما زلت نائماً في هذه الساعة؟
I'll come over for lunch.
سآتي لتناول الغداء.
Okay.
تمام.
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Before you see my husband,
قبل أن ترى زوجي،
I hope you'll
أتمنى أن تفعل
take a deep breath and brace yourself.
خذ نفسًا عميقًا واستعد.
When we meet again that day,
عندما نلتقي مجدداً في ذلك اليوم،
I'll definitely give you
سأعطيك بالتأكيد
a surprise you'll never forget.
مفاجأة لن تنساها أبداً.
You guessed it perfectly.
لقد خمنتَ الأمر بشكل مثالي.
Your brother really was shocked.
لقد صُدم أخوك حقاً.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪